export const flashcards = [
	{
		id: 1,
		front: "Árvore",
		back: "Tree",
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		front: "Janela",
		back: "Window",
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		front: "Porta",
		back: "Door",
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		front: "Parede",
		back: "Wall",
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		front: "Chão",
		back: "Floor",
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		front: "Cozinha",
		back: "Kitchen",
	},
	{
		id: 7,
		front: "Quarto",
		back: "Bedroom",
	}
];

export const flashcardsJson = [
	{
		"Árvore": {
			"id": 1,
			"front": "Árvore",
			"back": "Tree"
		}
	},
	{
		"Janela": {
			"id": 2,
			"front": "Janela",
			"back": "Window"
		}
	},
	{
		"Porta": {
			"id": 3,
			"front": "Porta",
			"back": "Door"
		}
	},
	{
		"Parede": {
			"id": 4,
			"front": "Parede",
			"back": "Wall"
		}
	},
	{
		"Chão": {
			"id": 5,
			"front": "Chão",
			"back": "Floor"
		}
	},
	{
		"Cozinha": {
			"id": 6,
			"front": "Cozinha",
			"back": "Kitchen"
		}
	},
	{
		"Quarto": {
			"id": 7,
			"front": "Quarto",
			"back": "Bedroom"
		}
	}
]